真正应该为
that those ultimately responsible
他女儿的死负责的人
for his daughter's death
在大众舆论中承担责任
are held accountable in the court of public opinion,
因为
since the Protection
合法武器经营保护法案
of Lawful Commerce in Arms Act
让他们在法庭上
precludes them from being held accountable
不用对此负责
in a court of law.
不好意思  这句话
Forgive me, is there
是不是少个名词
a noun missing?
格洛丽亚就是名词  法官阁下
Gloria's is the noun, Your Honor.
就是格洛丽亚枪械店出售了
Gloria's Guns is the gun shop that sold
用于谋杀我当事人女儿的那把半自动手枪
the semiautomatic handgun used to murder our client's daughter.
请节哀  先生
Ah. My condolences, sir.
而且该广告牌受第一修正案的保护
And the billboard is protected under the First Amendment.
不
No.
那是诽谤中伤  我们希望撤掉它
It's defamatory, and we want it taken down.
你能
Can you...